Doctor Mordrid will have you believing in magic all over again!
Doctor Mordrid is a fantasy, action, horror film directed by Albert Band.
Bound by hate and a mystical amulet that holds the powers of life and death, two immortal
wizards meet for the last time in an ancient struggle of good versus evil.
Dr. Mordrid, played by Jeffrey Combs.
Samantha Hunt, played by Yvette Nipar.
Tony Gaudio, played by Jay Acovone.
Adrian, played by Keith Coulouris.
Gunner, played by Ritch Brinkley.
Kabal, played by Brian Thompson.
Doctor Mordrid is a 1992 American superhero film directed by
Albert and Charles Band, and starring Jeffrey Combs.
The film was originally intended to be an adaptation of Marvel Comics' Doctor
Strange, but the studio's rights expired during pre-production.
Full Moon elected to still produce the movie, with the character
renamed, and enough other changes made to avoid a lawsuit.
The film explores themes of new york city,
teleportation, fight, time travel, amulet.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.